# **Luding Andrés Castañeda Gacía Software Developer**



#### **Contact**

✓ <u>ludingnumpaque@gmail.com</u>

+57 3193760301

in <u>Luding Castañeda</u>

#### **Skills**

#### **Backend technologies**

Python (Flask)

🦽 Ruby (Rails)

Js JavaScript (Express)

**Go** (Fiber)

#### Frontend technologies

5 Html, Css and JS

JavaScript (VueJS, ReactJS)

#### Other technologies

Docker (CI/CD)

Git (Github)

#### **Soft Skills**

Leadership

**2)** Communication

Planning

Agile methodologies (Scrum)

## **Profile**

I am a passionate Software Developer with experience working in the Web World, I really love work with new technologies and create creative solutions for problems using software as a tool. Usually I learn about innovation by testing Machine learning models or making mechanics in video games engines (commonly Godot), is part of my aventure spirit.

# **Professional Experience**

## **Full-Stack Developer**

Fusepong (Sep 2021 - Present)

I am working as Full-Stack using PostgreSQL and Rails in backend development, VueJS and Cordova in frontend development and docker with python for creating OS in micro-controllers and microservices connected with CI/CD Kubernetes. All focused in create an integrated ecosystem of innovation in Latam access control and security.

## **Web Developer**

Freelance (Jul 2019-Sep 2021)

I worked in a lot of independent or personal projects using de MERN stack (MoogoDB,Express,ReactJS,Node), using in some cases Handlebars like template motor (for fast projects without a big frontend requirement)

## **Education**

#### **Electronic Engineering**

<u>UNAD</u> (Universidad Nacional Abierta y a distancia) 2021 - Present

I am studying Electronic Engineering, I was learn C, C++ and VHDL focused in the implementation of micro-controllers and micro-processors, too I learned the process to design intermediate level integrated circuits for build simple electronic machines by myself

## **Technical Degree in Software Development**

SENA (Servicio Nacional deAprendizaje)

2019 - 2021

I studied software development, from logic think to advance algorism and POO, coding in Java and PHP